simpletexting.com 2016-12-01

# Privacy Policy - SimpleTexting.com

## SimpleTexting Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Statement sets forth the policies for, the collection and use of personally identifiable information (“Information”) by Made Simple Ventures LLC (“SimpleTexting”). This Statement covers the operation of its Web Site http://www.simpletexting.com (the “Site”) and its private label message services, operated on behalf of third parties (its “Clients”) and supersedes any previous statement of such policies. (The Site and private label service, are referred to collectively as the “Business” in this Statement.) SimpleTexting takes its obligations regarding privacy very seriously, and it wants to ensure Clients’ are fully informed about the Information they are providing. “Personally identifiable Information” refers to information that can identify an individual such as a name, or email address. Please address your questions about this Site, or Privacy Statement to privacy@simpletexting.com.

### Collection of Information

We collect personal information on the Site to facilitate the services offered to you during your use of the Business. Clients’ must register an account on the Site prior to having access to any of the services. To register an account on the Site, we may require name, email, phone number and physical address information, as well as sensitive financial information including credit card numbers to process the registration. Where applicable, we also collect third party personal information if the registered administrator is different from the initiator of the registration for the service. By registering for the service, the platform exists for Clients’ to enter third party personal information into their account for the purpose of using the Business services, this information may include, but is not limited to cellular phone numbers, associated names, notes, and email addresses. None of this personal information is used for any promotional purposes, or shared with third parties for their promotional purposes by SimpleTexting. SimpleTexting may also collect non-personally identifiable information from Clients’ via “cookies” (small text files placed by SimpleTexting on user computers), single-pixel GIF image files (also called “Web beacons”), Web server log analysis and other similar technological means. We also receive website navigational information such as IP address and referring URL when our Site is visited. Such information may be used to track site trends and enhance the user experience, and may be shared with third parties in aggregated, non personally identifiable form. To the extent third parties may place advertising on the Site, such third parties may use cookies, or other technological means within the advertising to collect and use non-personally identifiable information. SimpleTexting is not responsible for information collected by third parties in this manner, nor for the collection or use of Information by other sites to which the Site is linked.

### No Collection of Information from Children

This Site is not intended for users under the age of 18, nor does SimpleTexting knowingly collect, or retain Information from children under the age of 13.

### Use of Information

SimpleTexting uses Information collected in connection with the Site in the following ways:

  1. To provide requested information, products and services to users via the Site.
  2. To improve the user experience with the Sites
  3. In connection with the operation of the Sites
  4. For users to obtain information and offers for products and services offered by SimpleTexting.

### Security

SimpleTexting uses industry accepted electronic and physical standards of security to reduce the risk of improper access to or manipulation of Information during transmission and storage. We employ the use of SSL [Secure Socket Layer] technology to protect your sensitive information during transmission. While we take every precaution to guarantee safety, no method of security is 100% effective and we encourage you to employ discretion when submitting your information.

### Information Sharing

SimpleTexting may be legally obligated to disclose information to the government or to third parties under certain circumstances, such as illegal activity on our Site. SimpleTexting reserves the right to release personal information to its service providers, law enforcement, or other government officials, or in response to a formal request in a civil action, Court order or judicial proceeding as we, in our sole and absolute discretion, deems necessary or appropriate. Moreover, in the event of a merger, sale, or acquisition of some, or all of SimpleTexting’s assets, your personal information could be part of the transferred assets. In such an event, we shall notify you by a notice on the home page. Any changes to the information practices governing your information & your choices would be noted. The Site employs the use of a third party payment processor to process payments made to us. This third party is not authorized to use this information for any purposes beyond facilitating this service on our behalf. We post customer testimonials on our Site that may include a user’s name and email [not displayed]. We obtain permission of our Clients’ prior to posting their testimonials on our Site. When you select to comment on a blog post, please be aware that any personal information you submit therein shall be available publicly to other users of the Site & can be used to send unsolicited messages. SimpleTexting is not responsible for the personal information a user selects to disclose in a public forum.

### Opting Out from Offers from SimpleTexting

You may opt-out of receiving our newsletters by clicking on the opt-out link included in every email newsletter we send, or by contacting privacy@simpletexting.com. SimpleTexting service offerings include acting as a service provider for our clients’ in providing an “opt-out” platform for their recipients [end users]. At any time, recipients [end users] may discontinue receiving SMS offers by sending the SMS message “STOP” to the applicable shortcode. Additionally, end users’ may discontinue receiving offers from a particular client by sending the SMS message STOP to that Client’s particular shortcode, or by following other instructions provided by that Client. Opting out from a particular Client’s offers will not apply to any communications from other Clients. All information provided to SimpleTexting’s clients is owned by said client and subject to their privacy statement. We are not responsible for their privacy practices during our role as the clients’ service provider.

### Access to Information

All Clients’ who provide their Information to SimpleTexting may modify and correct such Information by e-mailing us at support@simpletexting.com and registered Clients’ can modify their personal information and accounts by logging into their accounts on our home page and modifying their preferences.

### California Privacy Rights

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of SimpleTexting who are California residents to request certain information regarding SimpleTexting’s disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to: support@simpletexting.com.

Changes to this Privacy Policy SimpleTexting reserves the right to revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such revisions will be effective on the date of posting to the Site, and will apply to all information collected by SimpleTexting both prior to, and following the effective date. Your use of the Site following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions. Users should periodically visit this page to review the current policies with regard to Information. Should we make a material change to the manner in which we collect, use or store information collected on our Site, we shall notify you via system notification upon login.

### Contacting Us

You can contact SimpleTexting with your questions and concerns at: support@simpletexting.com.  
Or by Mail at  **3250 NE 1st Avenue, Suite 305, Miami, FL 33137 ATT: SimpleTexting Compliance**

Effective November 23, 2016
